Amaya Mali

512.695.6794

amaya.mali3@gmail.com

3833 Nobel Dr. apt# 3201 San Diego, CA

linkedin.com/in/amayasm

amayamali3.wixsite.com/myportfolio

Skills

Photoshop CC Illustrator Indesign Invision Sketch XD **CSS** Java HTML Pvthon Premiere Pro Final Cut Pro

After Effects

Coursework

Design Of Everyday Things Data Science and Practice Introduction to Computer Science and Object Oriented Programing

About Me

I am fascinated with the intersection of intelligent design and human behavior. I have been drawn to design since I was a freshman in high school. Currently, I am a third year at University of California - San Diego, Studying Cognitive Science and minoring in Design. I am fascinated with the challenge of designing user centered products by understanding human behavior. I plan to use linguistics and psychology with experience and practice in design to solve these problems. I have experience with graphic design, user interaction design, user experience design and research. I want to gain more experience with

management.

Education -

University of California - San Diego | In progress Major: Bachelor of Science in Cognitive Science Minor: Design

user research, user experience and product

Professional Experience

Al-Global.org Design Intern | June 2019 - Present

Researched and Designed main website

Conducted user testing and protyping on the application

Moores Cancer Center Web Developer Assistant | August 2019 - Present Presented research with 3 designed mockups Developed full website for potential

Center for Applied Internet and Data Analysis Graphic Design Intern | April 2019 - Present

Designed 2 logos for research projects Updated graphics for physical displays

Winkielman Lab

Research Assistant | January 2019 - Present

Assisted with study participants and discussions Assisted with EMG studies, and data collection

Swing Golf App Startup

UX Designer | August 2018 - February 2019

Conducted user research at golf ranges Designed mockups of the tutorial demo

CognitiveScale

UI Design Intern I June 2017 to July 2017 Designed a UI demo of a calendar for a hospital Researched top AI trends in user interface Completed a Design Thinking Workshop

Extracurricular

Design For America - UCSD

Design Education Internal Lead | May 2019 - Present

Team Member | October 2018 - Present

Designed an app to help students with mental

Conducted research on college students Gathered insights and redesigned the application

Cogntive Science Student Association

Executive in Logistics | May 2019 - Present External Public Relations | May 2018 - Present

Organized and registered rooms for events Used Illustrator to create logos and t-shirts for national conference